ACUÑA, KIMBERLY ANN R.

257 Capt. Ciano R. Balderamma St. Ibayo Tipas, Taguig City +639173898342 kimberlyannacuna@gmail.com



AIM

My goal is to add and create value in supporting an organization's business goals through my skills and expertise. I envision charting in this organization a long-term career plan that will allow me not just to grow others but likewise ensure my own development.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATION

Eight years of work experience – provides Direction and Leadership, manages employees' performance, motivate a team to achieve targets and objectives of continuously improving quality of products and services increasing store revenues and improve profitability.

Has Good Communication Skills; Basic knowledge in Baking, Food Sanitation and Safety, Proficient in the use of the following softwares: Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word and Microsoft Powerpoint, Can adapt easily to different working environment and can work under extreme pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

 Single Origin Coffee and Tea Inc. Single Origin Operations Manager June 2017 - Present

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible to attain optimum profitability from the operations of all restaurants by providing delightful customer service, quality products and ensuring operational excellence in accordance with established company policies, systems, procedures and standards.
- Foodparks by Raintree Stella and Rocketroom Restaurant Manager

October 2015 – June 2017

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible in creating the tone and personality of the store by being an advocate of training, customer service, product knowledge and education, encouraging safe work practices, and a demonstrated commitment through the Guiding Principles. Lead all Team Members in an efficient and profitable operation.
- Global Restaurant Concepts Inc.
 Gyu-kaku Japanese BBQ Restaurant Restaurant Manager

February 2015 - October 2015

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible in creating the tone and personality of the store by being an advocate of training, customer service, product knowledge and education, encouraging safe work practices, and a demonstrated commitment through the Guiding Principles. Lead all Team Members in an efficient and profitable operation.
- Global Restaurant Concepts Inc.
 Godiva Philippines (City of Dreams Manila)
 Shift Manager

November 2014 - February 2015

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible for opening the first store in the Philippines, in charged with ordering of imported and local ingredients. Exposed and trained in Hong Kong with their daily operations, sanitation and customer service of the retail stores.
- The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf Phils. Inc. District Manager

January 2013 - July 2014

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible for directing and educating the Store Managers and Lead Shift Supervisors within a specified district in the daily operations, sales and customer service of the retail stores. Fulfills duties assigned by Operations Manager / Director.

• The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf Phils. Inc. Store Manager

July 2012 - January 2013

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible in creating the tone and personality of the store by being an advocate of training, customer service , product knowledge and education, encouraging safe work practices, and a demonstrated commitment through the Guiding Principles. Lead all Team Members in an efficient and profitable operation.
- The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf Phils. Inc. Shift Supervisor

July 2011 - July 2012

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible for the supervision of the Baristas in maintaining the quality of service and product. It enforces all procedures in the absence of the Store Manager.

• The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf Phils. Inc.

June 2011 - July 2011

Barista

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Responsible for serving all products with friendly, individualized attention towards each customer. Educate customers about the products.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

• B.S Hospitality Management 2007- 2011
Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig (College Level)

Best in Feasibility, Dean's Lister and Cum Laude

Rizal High School
 Pasig City
 Class, Top 1
 2003-2007
 (Secondary Level)

Precious Academy
 Taguig City
 Class, Valedictorian
 1998-2003
 (Primary Level)

SEMINARS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

✓ Tea Seminar with David de Candia (May 2013)

- ✓ In House Training: Customer Service 101(The Coffee Bean Way), Customer Service 102 (Creating Magic Moments)
- ✓ In House Training: World of Coffee and Tea (Coffee and Tea Background)

PERSONAL INFORMATION

BIRTH DATE: April 7, 1991 AGE: 28 years old

HEIGHT: 5'2"
WEIGHT: 52 kg.
GENDER: Female
CIVIL STATUS: Single
RELIGION: Christian

HOBBIES: Reading books, Travelling

CHARACTER REFERENCES

Ms. Luisa del Rosario
Operations Director
Global Restaurants Concepts Inc.
+63 9178694888

Ms. Rhona Coronel
Operations Director
Foodparks by Raintree Inc.
+63 9175709020

I hereby certify that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Kimberly Ann R. Acuña